admanager-xertive.com 2014-06-25

# Xertive Media - Privacy Policy

## Our Commitment

Xertive Media is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement outlines the types of information we gather through our technology as well as the steps we take to keep that information safe.

## Your IP address

An IP (Internet Protocol) address is automatically assigned to your computer every time you establish a connection on the Internet. Xertive Media uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. When you open an account on Xertive Media, your ip address will be associated with personally identifiable information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file.

## Third Party Cookies

Our clients' advertisements are displayed on many Internet sites ("Publishers"). In some cases, these Publishers may also place a cookie on your browser. In the course of delivering an ad to you, the third party ad serving party may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser and use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

## Data

Notwithstanding any other provision, we may also engage a data provider who may collect web log data from you (including IP address and information about your browser or operating system), or place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, that we may share with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these data provider cookies, please go to <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

## Opt Out

If you do not want the benefits of cookies, there is a simple procedure that allows you to deny or accept this feature. In order to "opt out" of the benefits of cookies, you may manually delete your cookies by following the instructions contained in the Help section of your browser.

## Children Under 13 Years of Age

In light of the concern over protecting children's privacy online, Xertive Media Agency does not knowingly request, collect, or share personally identifiable information from users under the age of 13. Our websites, products and services are neither developed for, nor directed at, children.

## How to Contact Us

Should there be any questions or suggestions regarding the privacy policy, the support desk can be contacted [here](http://xertivemedia.com/contact-us/).
